(Katee Sackhoff:)Sorry,
(Bernadette:)I had to clock out.
(Howard:)Oh, no, that's okay.
(Howard:)How have you been?
(Bernadette:)Okay. You know,
busy, schoolwork. You?
(Howard:)Same. I took a scuba-diving
course over the summer,
(Howard:)but it turns out I'm
terrified of the ocean.
(Bernadette:)Too bad.
(Howard:)You wouldn't know anybody
who wants to buy a wet
suit, boy's large?
(Howard:)Yeah, forget it.
Not important.
(Howard:)So, are you
seeing anyone?
(Bernadette:)Well, to be honest, I...
Hey, how are we
(Penny:)doing over here? Can I
get you something to drink?
(Howard:)Not for me, thanks.
I'm okay.
(Penny:)Are you gonna want
to order food?
(Howard:)Maybe later.
Okay.
(Howard:)So, are you seeing anybody?
(Raj:)No.
(Penny:)That's what I told him
when he asked me.
(Penny:)I hope that's not out of line.
(Bernadette:)No, it's fine.
Penny, can we have
a little privacy?
(Penny:)Oh. I'm sorry.
(Bernadette:)What about you,
have you been seeing anybody?
(Howard:)Well, you know
how it is with guys.